Why don't
you tell us what you're working on?
Computing is bits plus neurons,
plus qubits.
We're in a really exciting time
for quantum,
where we're having co-development
of applications, theory
and hardware.
We have new fridges
now that have a modular configuration.
Right now
we're a touch below 20 millikelvin.
We get to create an AI architecture
from scratch in AI.
We need different perspectives
represented.
Open source is the way to go.
All levels of our technology
stack are here.
Not only will these technologies continue
to mature and provide value on their own,
but in the next five years, we'll see
meaningful intersection points
between these technologies.
Every year, something happens
that I would not have believed possible.
What's next?
What's next? What's next? What's next?
What's next in computing
is democratized open technology, quantum
coherently coupled processors,
seamless computing.
What amazes me the most
is that we have gone this far,
but that we keep going further.